we are being shelled by the Poles, the Moldovans Yes, but
нас обстреливают поляки молдаване Да но
we are not aggressive on them, and the Russians are
мы на них не агрессивные а русские с
friends with us, but for some reason we are aggressive on them.
нами дружат так но мы на них почему-то
Why
агрессивные Почему
so honestly, I didn’t even know that the
так честно я даже не знал о том что вас
Poles were shelling you Oh, hello, good afternoon, how are
поляки О здравствуйте Добрый день Как
you doing? It’s normal, I’m from Ukraine, city
ваши дела Нормально я из Украины город
Khmelnitsky Where are you from? The Republic of
Хмельницкий А вы откуда Республика
Dagestan, the city of Kakva Sla,
Дагестан город каква сла
Makhachkala,
Махачкала
or Who are you, Dorgi, Avar, godfather, who am I, you are
или А вы кто дорги аварец кумы кто я ти
Greek, and
грек и
Ava, your parents are Greek, how did you get there?  they
ава родители греки как попали они там
already lived there
жили уже
Yes no they moved here During the Soviet
Да нет они переехали сюда При Советском
Union No no after Dep year a What did you
Союзе Нет нет после Деп год а Что
move
переехали
specifically
специально
choose yes yes And what are you talking about With the
выбираете да да А о чём Говорите С
Ukrainians they are trying to explain to them that their
украинцами пытаются им объяснить что их
aggressive attitude is wrong, like
агрессивный настрой Это неправильно типа
we are all friends, everything is cool Super
мы все друзья френдли всё классно Супер
Dada I'm here  I also don’t understand, look, I
Дада Я вот тоже не понимаю смотрите Я
just went to chat roulette and I don’t understand
вот вышел в чат рулетку и я не понимаю
why my compatriots are so
почему мои соотечественники такие
aggressive towards Russians, that’s what you
агрессивные к россиянам вот как вы
think, why I want to
думаете почему я хочу
figure it out Well, apparently they’re looking at more  the
разобраться Ну видимо смотрят на более
adult generation and they can’t
взрослое поколение и не могут сами
think for themselves you can’t for some reason, that is, the
мыслить ти сами не могут почему то есть
older generation is aggressive towards the
более взрослое поколение агрессивно к
Russians Yes, most likely And why
россиянам Да скорее всего А почему
why is this what happened We, for example, are not
почему вот что случилось Мы например не
aggressive towards the Poles not aggressive towards the
агрессивны к полякам не агрессивны к
Moldovans but are aggressive towards the Russians
молдаванам но агрессивны к россиянам
Why is it that you asked me  Yes,
Почему так это вы у меня спрашивали Да
well, that’s what you think
ну вот как вы думаете что такое
happened. Why are we aggressive towards the Russians?
случилось Почему мы именно к россиянам
Honestly, I don’t know, everyone’s
агрессивные Честно не знаю скучно всем
life is boring, so they decided to somehow diversify
жить вот они решили както разнообразить
their life, I
свою
just see that the Poles are shelling us
просто смотрю что нас обстреливают
Moldovans Yes, but we are not aggressive towards them,
поляки молдаване Да но мы на них не
and the Russians are friends with us,
агрессивные а русские с нами дружат так
but for some reason we are aggressive towards them.
но мы на них почему-то агрессивные
Why
Почему
so honestly, I didn’t even know that
так честно я даже не знал о том что вас
the Poles were firing at you? Well, look now,
обстреливают поляки Ну смотрите сейчас
right now Poland and
сейчас же в Украине идёт Польша и
Moldova are carrying out a special military
Молдова сделали специальную военную
operation in Ukraine  against Ukraine so yes, we are
операцию против Украины так во Да мы
now at war with Poland and Moldova, Russia
сейчас воюем с Польшей и Молдовой Россия
helps us with weapons, for example, and
нам помогает оружием так например и
equipment,
техникой
and I don’t
лями и я не
understand why, why are we then angry with the
пони Почему почему мы тогда злимся на
Russians and not with the Poles and  Moldovans
русских а не на Поляков и молдован
who attacked us What do you
которые На нас напали Как вы
think you see exactly want the Cape somehow
думаете видите именно хотите мыс как-то
locally globally globally Cape
локально глобально глобально мыс
look at the EU think globally then
смотрите ЕС глобально мыслить то
Poland and Moldova attacked Yes but why are the
напала Польша и Молдова Да но почему
Ukrainians angry not at the Poles and Moldovans
украинцы злятся не на Поляков и молдован
But at Russia which
А на Россию которая нам
helps us look Polish missiles are bombing
помогает смотрите польские ракеты бомбят
Dnepropetrovsk Yes  Moldova
Днепропетровск Да Молдова
has caught up with the Russians. Why let's
сравнялась на русских Почему немного
change the topic a little. You're someone by profession,
сменим тему Вот вы по профессии кто нене
look again, let's get to
ещё раз смотрите давайте мы уже до
let’s look at this topic since we started, that is,
разберём эту тему раз мы начали то есть
look Russia. I also don’t understand
смотрите Россия Вот я тоже не понимаю
why we are aggressive towards Russia, the
почему мы агрессивно настроены к Росси
Poles are bombing our cities. I’m not even talking about this,
поляки бомбят наши города Я даже об этом
why do you want to talk about a topic in
почему вы хотите говорить на ту тему в
which a person is not relevant? I’m not
которой человек не актуален я не
relevant in this topic, so I’m not  you
актуален в этой теме так вот не вы вы же
raised this topic, why is it aggressive here? I’m
подняли эту тему Почему тут агрессивно Я
saying that’s what you asked, why did
же говорю вот что что вы спросили почему
I choose Ukraine, I’m telling you? I
я выбрал именно Украину я вам говорю Я
’m trying to explain that this
пытаюсь объяснить то что вот этот
attitude is wrong, we’re all
настрой - Это неправильно мы все френдли
really friendly, actually really friendly. Yes, fly  Friendly
вообще реально френдли Да фли Friendly
Friendly look Mariupol Mariupol
Friendly смотрите Мариуполь Мариуполь
was destroyed too Friendly Friendly
уничтожили тоже такие ли Friendly
That's what I'm talking about the adult
Вот вот о чём я и говорю взрослое
generation Here you are the adult generation
поколение Вот вы взрослое поколение у
you have some kind of mood you you you hear but
вас настрой какой-то вы вы вы слышите но
don't listen really look we're
не слушайте реально смотрите мы
zombied we understand I want to convey to everyone I
зомбированный нам понимаете Я всем Я
want to convey look Russia  - this is a friend of
хочу донести смотрите Россия - это друг
Russia, not Russia is shooting at us, because we
Россия не россие по нам стреляет ведь мы
all see that Moldova and Poland
же все видим год что Молдова и Польша
are bombing our cities Yes, Moldova has been razed to
бомбят наши города Да Молдова сравнялась
the ground  Mariupol And we are somehow angry with the
землёй Мариуполь А мы что-то злимся на
Russians Russia says nli fli friendly and
россиян Россия говорит нли фли френдли а
we are angry with the Russians Why why is
мы злимся на на россиян Почему почему
you a simple guy in Dagestan, you
выж простой парень в Дагестане вот нам
just wish us well, friendly friendly and the
только желаете добра френдли френдли а
Poles and Moldovans are sitting, we will capture you
поляки и молдаване сидят мы вас захватим
because you are determined too or their
потому что вы настроены тоже или их
government  that’s the mood Well, they look
правительство так настро Ну они смотрите
I don’t know One way or another, but I see the fact
Я не знаю Так или не так но я вижу факт
that Poland and Moldova are bombing Ukraine
да что Польша и Молдова бомбит Украину
Yes, and Russia is helping us with weapons so that
Да а Россия помогает нам оружием чтобы
we can fight against  Poles and Moldovans,
мы воевали против Поляков и молдован
it’s true, you knew about the war. Well,
правда вы знали о войне Ну так же не ещё
look again, it’s true, and Russia is not at war
раз смотрите правда тож Россия не воюет
with Ukraine, it’s true, I don’t know who I
с Украиной правда я не знаю что с кем
grew up with. Here I am, well, what do you
вообще рос Вот вот я же ну как вы
think? You, as a citizen of Russia, your
считаете вы как гражданин России ваша
country is not at war with Ukraine. Truth.  she
страна не воюет с Украиной Правда она ей
only helps her with weapons, it’s true that Russia
только помогает оружием правда Россия
only helps with weapons, she doesn’t fight because,
только помогает оружием не воюет потому
well, in Ukraine, look, Russia doesn’t
что ну в Украине смотрите Россия не
shell Ukrainian cities. Yes, but for
обстреливает украинские города Да а вот
example, Poland and Moldova are shelling,
например Польша и Молдова обстреливают
let me answer this way, but I don’t feel comfortable about
давайте так отвечу а мне мне неприятно э
that A  why is it unpleasant for you because
те А почему тебе неприятно потому что
war is bad I’m a pacifist so yes you’re
война - это плохо я пацифист так да ты
a pacifist Yes but you don’t understand something
пацифист Да но ты что-то не понимаешь
Come on
Давай
so you don’t understand why Ukrainians
так ты не понимаешь почему украинцы
are angry with
злятся на
you and you don’t think why your
тебя а ты не думаешь почему твои
compatriots are angry with Ukrainians and
соотечественники злятся на украинцев и
want to capture and kill
хотят захватить и убивают
Ukrainians I  the
украинцев Я так и знал
prince knew why poison,
кня кчему яду
but I’m not opposed to Russia in order to
та вот я не настроен против России дабы
bring me into dialogue, I’ll tell you this.
вывести меня на диалог я вам так скажу
It’s because of provocateurs like you that
Вот из-за таких провокаторов как вы
I’m still  provocateur Yes indeed, you
всё-таки я провокатор Да действительно
know exactly, people come to them, a
Вот именно знаете люди им прилетает
Russian missile flies in, they are so
Российская ракета они такие они такие
fluffy, and then such a provocateur comes out and
фли а выходит потом такой провокатор
says Hey dudes, it’s a Russian
говорит Эй чуваки это же Российская
missile that destroyed your house, they’re like that, don’t
ракета уничтожила Ваш дом они такие не
provoke them, Friendly Friendly Russia
провоцируй мыли Friendly Friendly Россия
FR And I’m like a provocateur, I come out again,
FR А я такой как провокатор выхожу ещ
dudes, this is Russia  they will destroy shi,
чуваки это Россия уничтожат ши
dude, don’t
они чувак не
bother me, you understand, honestly tell me, you’re not
мешай понимаете Честно скажите вам не
ashamed, you’re not ashamed at all. I see that you’re
стыдно вообще не стыдно Я смотрю что Вы
cynical.
циничные Вот вы
You shouldn’t be for reasons of conscience
ни по соображениям совести вам должно
I’m ashamed of everything that you do I’m
быть стыдно за всё то что вы делаете Я я
proud I’m proud that I’m provoking
горжусь Я горжусь что я провоцирую
look and people like us We are Ukrainians And
смотрите и такие как Мы украинцы И
Russians should all provoke you to
россияне все должны провоцировать
turn on your brain Yes because such
включать мозг Да потому что такие
cynical ones for example come out and say
циничные например выходит и говорят
our countries Yes Mariupol was destroyed
наши страны Да Мариуполь уничтожили
Friendly Friendly Yes in Kramatorsk
Friendly Friendly Да в Краматорске
they got into the house  Friendly Friendly missiles in
попали в дом ракеты Friendly Friendly в
Dnepropetrovsk demolished two entrances
Днепропетровске снесли два подъезда
Friendly Friendly so I’ll tell you what
Friendly Friendly так вот я тебе вот что
when when the Empire will mobile you
скажу когда когда Империя мобилие тебя и
wrap yours around the caterpillar of
будет наматывать твои на гусеницу
some tank yes Then I will sit and
какого-то танка да Тогда я буду сидеть и
tell you like our generation
говорит тебе подобно наше поколение всё
will change everything for yours This is who our young
изменит ваше Это кто наше молодое
generation is What How old are you children
поколение Какое Сколько тебе лет дети
of the two thousandth They are how old are you children of the
двухтысячных Они сколько тебе лет детё
2000s
2000х
23 children of the two thousandth are now entering
23 дети двухтысячных поступают сейчас в
Makeyevka at a vocational school you know here  there is a vocational school there
Макеевку в ПТУ знаете вот там есть ПТУ
just for the children of the 2000s from Russia,
как раз для детей двухтысячных из России
massively shorter, there are no entrance
массово короче там без вступительных
exams, but with accelerated graduation there is
экзаменов но с ускоренным выпускным есть
this and these Children  Yes,
такое и вот такие Дети дся да которые
whose country kills people in a foreign
страна которых убивает людей в чужой
country and they sit and pretend to be
стране а они сидят и делают из себя
so cynical. Although maybe they don’t. The
такого циничного Хотя может не делают
point is that to make a fool of yourself, you
Дело в том что делать из себя дурачка
have to be not a fool to make a
надо быть не дурачком чтобы делать из
fool of yourself, so this is a moot point,
себя дурачка поэтому это спорный вопрос
yes, continue, not me already  spoke out I
да продолжайте не я уже высказался Я
now want you to say something, I’ll
хочу теперь чтобы вы что-то сказали я
then
дальше
start your aggressive
начну ваш агрессивный
attitude, I’ll have a constructive dialogue with
настрой мне конструктивный диалог с
you and you initially had such an
вами и у вас изначально был такой
attitude, I don’t know how to ride with someone
настрой это я не знаю с кем-то
Yes, this is yours  the scheme is
прокатывать Да вот это ваша схема
first like a fairy tale, first a lubricant and
сначала типа сказочка сначала смазочка а
then a fairy tale. Why is Poland
потом сказочка Да почему вот Польша
bombing so that I agree and you’re like that, you
бомбит чтобы я согласился и вы такой ну
know? But
знаешь А вот
you, I’m for peace in the whole world and yours,
вы я за мир во всём мире и вашем вот
apparently it’s not in vain that Russia does this since there are
видимо не зря Россия так делает раз
provocateurs like you there and I
такие как вы провокаторы там есть и Я
think  and justice will get to you Yeah, you
думаю и до вас доберётся правосудие Угу
know what I'm talking about, I'll say it Look,
понимаете о чём я говорю я скажу Смотри
you're a blogger who hypes on the deaths of
ты блогер который хайпует на смертях
people in Chui Country, I listened to you, don't
людей в Чуй стране я тебя выслушал не
interrupt T Child  two-thousandth computer,
перебивай Т Дитё двухтысячных компьютер
don’t interrupt the child of the two-thousandth Listen,
да не перебивай детё двухтысячных Слушай
and you are now listening to your public,
а вы сейчас на свою публику слуша слу
listen to me, don’t interrupt me, I
слушай меня да же не перебивай я тебя
listened to you, I didn’t interrupt, I listened. You’re
выслушал я не перебивал послушал Вот ты
hype You’re having fun, yes, but when will it
хайпует Тебе весело да но когда тебя
mobilize you because the Empire will reach
мобилизует потому что Империя дойдёт до
you Yes, it will get Uno I  I’ll even
тебя Да она достанет Уно Я даже
try, maybe I can help the empire
постараюсь может помочь империи
realize your
реализовать твои
pacifist provocateurs like me, yes we
пацифистских провокаторов как я да мы
must provoke provoke and
должны провоцировать провоцировать и
provoke like that  because
провоцировать так потому что
don’t interrupt Don’t podgora because it’s
не перебивай Не подгора потому что
only our provocation Yes it turns on the brains of
только наша провокация Да включает мозг
people not only here but throughout Russia
людей не только у нас а и во всей России
and in three years you will think
так и лет через три ты будешь думать
How moral I was Although in order to
Каким я был моральным Хотя для того
think like that you need to understand I don’t
чтобы так думать надо понимать Я не
think maybe you  and you won’t
думаю может может ты и не будешь
understand because a person who
понимать потому что человек который
remains, for example, a moral monster, he
остаётся например моральным уродом он не
cannot understand that he was a moral monster,
может понять что он был моральным уродом
that by your standards I am
что по вашим меркам Я
morally against the war and against what is
морально против войны и против того что
happening now No no, you are for the war, you will
сейчас происходит Нет нет вы за войну вы
justify the terror of the Russian Federation in
оправдайте террор Российской Федерации в
Ukraine  yes At what point did I justify the
Украине да В каком моменте я оправдал
terror of the Russian fi Well look from
террор российской фи Хорошо смотри из
what you say yes you blame us as
того что вы говорите да вы обвиняете нас
victims of aggression instead of blaming the
жертв агрессии так а не обвиняете
aggressor you took the words out of No
агрессора вы вырвали слова из Нет ещё
again look at any here any
раз смотри любое вот любое
spreads the blame somewhere on the victims
размазывает или вины куда-то на жертв
this is aggression  come on, who is to blame
это и есть агресси давай так кто виноват
for the fact that Putin attacked
в том что Путин напал на
Ukraine, I don’t know, I’m not a politician, well, I’m
Украину я не знаю я не политик Вот вот
not a politician, yes, that’s who you are, and here’s
не политик Да вот так кто ви А вот как
how. Let’s look again, let’s think about how  just
Давай ещё раз смотри подумаем как просто
like just a kid Yes, just like
как просто пацанчик Да как просто
a kid,
пацанчик
tell me if Russia attacked Ukraine Who is
скажи если Россия напала на Украину Кто
to blame that Russia attacked Ukraine Who is
виноват что Россия напала на Украину Кто
to blame for Russia attacking Ukraine who is
виноват Россия напала на Украину кто
to blame for this when Russia attacked You
виноват в этом когда Россия напала Вот
see, I’m saying You’re cynical Yes, you’re
видишь я же говорю Вот ты циничная Да ты
moral Well Well It’s obvious  if you
мораль Ну Ну Это же очевидно если ты
say And when Russia attacked
говоришь А когда Россия напала на
Ukraine It’s obvious February that the
Украину Это очевидно февраля то что
beginning of the special is not not I’m saying look, it’s
начало спец не не я же говорю смотри то
clear that you’re moral, so why are you
видно что ты морально что что ж ты
arguing? That is, you’re trying to
споришь То есть ты ты себя пробуешь
do it yourself Well, it’s obvious in general
делать Ну это же очевидно вообще
no, you have to be a fool, you have to have intelligence Well, look, you
нет дурачком надо иметь ум Ну смотри Ты
see, we are watching. So you start
видишь мы смотрим Так что ты начинаешь
pretending to be there, that is, you
там строить из себя то есть ты всё
understand everything that is happening Yes, but you act like
понимаешь что происходит Да но ты себя
that, that is, people at your age
дееь так то есть люди в твоём возрасте
Yes, they are already thinking How, for example, to
Да уже думают Как там например бизнес
start a business Yes, for example, a job
начать Да как например работу хорошую
find a good one How to realize your
найти Как реализовать свой жизненный
potential in life So you sit there and go to chat
потенциал Так а ты сидишь выходишь в чат
roulette to troll there.
рулетку для того чтобы там потроллить
People my age know
Украин знают люди в моём возрасте думают
how to start a business. And I’m like, I go to
Как начать бизнес А я типажу захожу в
Roulette and  I’m doing provocations right Well,
Рулетку и провокацией занимаюсь верно Ну
yes, you suffer
да страдаешь
like the strength of your age, even you are
как силу своего возраста даже Вы
very yes And you are a luminary of mind, I’ll explain to
очень да А ты светила ума я объясню
me I have a lot of friends in Ukraine,
мне У меня очень много друзей в Украине
I’ve been there myself, I have a lot of
я сам там бывал у меня очень много
athletes from Ukraine, everything from
спортсменов с Украины всё вот там
my past is that I went in for
прошлого моего то что я занимался
sports and  I’m doing this computer club,
спортом а вот этот компьютерный клуб им
I’m thinking about business, I’m
занимаюсь я я думаю о бизнесе мне это
not interested in all this and I’m against it. I’m in
всё не интересно и я против этого Я за
favor of sitting down and talking peacefully.
то чтобы сели поговорили мирным путём
21st century. So who’s to blame? Well, who
XXI век Так а кто виноват ну кто с кем
should sit down and talk with whom? What I mean is that at the
должен сесть поговорить Я к тому что в
moment you  incompetent to the
данный момент вы некомпетентный до
point of horror who I don’t even understand I’m super
ужаса который даже не понимаю я супер
super incompetent yes tell me tell
супер некомпетентный да скажи мне скажи
me incompetent and who should
мне некомпетентно а кто с кем должен
sit down and talk with whom he says I’m in favor of
сесть и поговорить вот говорит Я за то
sitting down and talking who should talk to whom you
чтобы сели и поговорили кто с кем должен
know because of these people I’m
поговорить знаете вот из-за таких Я же
telling you who  with whom did you say,
вам говорю кто с кем вот ты же сказал
look, you said then you say I’m
смотри ты сказал то ты говоришь
not interested in politics and now you
политикой не интересуюсь а теперь
say I’m in favor of sitting down and talking.
говоришь Я за то чтоб сели и поговорили
And who should sit down and talk and talk
А кто должен сесть и поговорить
and on your part there from Ukraine
и и с вашей стороны там с Украины
the youth of Ukraine and the youth of Russia who
молодёжь Украины и молодёжь России кто
should sit down and talk to
должен сесть и поговорить чтобы
stop this war
остановить эту войну провокаторов
old provocateurs should sit down and talk to
старых должен сесть и поговорить чтобы
stop this
остановить эту
war who should sit down and talk
войну кто должен сесть и поговорить
to stop this war when you know
чтобы остановить эту войну когда знаешь
how it turns out I answer you one
как получается я отвечаю тебе на один
question When you don’t like the answer you
вопрос Когда тебе не нравится ответ ты
ask  another question about those No,
задаёшь другой вопро те го Нет ты ты
look, you are saying that you are out of politics And
смотри ты говоришь что ты вне политики А
here you are telling politics that we need to sit down
тут ты политике говоришь что надо сесть
and talk, who should sit down and to
и поговорить кто должен сесть и чтобы
stop this war, me you or Zelensky
остановить эту войну я ты или Зеленский
Poroshenko or Biden Sipin
Порошенко или байден сипин
who
кто кто
should who  who should
должен кто должен
talk war
поговорить войну
Come on Listen here my friends are indignant about
Давай Слушай тут мои друзья негодуют по
the fact that I’m
тому поводу что я с таким человеком как
even having a dialogue with a person like you I don’t care at all
ты вообще веду диалог мне вообще пофиг
if for you you don’t have your
сри если для тебя у тебя нет своего
own personal opinion they will talk about you
личного мнения на тебе будут говорять
there lead Don’t lead then who you are You don’t even  You
там веди Не веди то кто ты такой Ты даже
don’t know how to
личного мнения своё не умеешь
listen to the opinions of others You
прислушивайтесь к мнению других У вас
only have no I’ll say it again That is, you
только е я ещё раз говорю То есть ты
don’t even have your own opinion They’ll tell you
даже своё мнения не имеешь тебе скажут
something like Why are you talking to him You
типа А что ты с ним говоришь ты уже
just want a shortcut You want you to answer
просто хочешь среза ты хочешь ты ответь
me  question Who should sit down and
мне на вопрос Кто должен сесть и
talk Come on, who should talk from the session
поговорить Давай кто должен с сессии
to stop the war, that’s all on
поговорить чтобы остановить войну всё на
this Come on, who should talk to the session
этом Давай кто должен сессии поговорить
to stop the war who started it,
чтобы остановить войну тот кто её затеял
who And who started it wrong, you said
та кто А кто её затеял не так ты сказал
what are you for or did they talk So
что ты за то чтоли поговорили Так
who am I  I’m saying those who
кто я же говорю те кто её
started it. That is, you don’t know who started it, but
зате То есть ты не знаешь кто затеял но
you say that they need to sit down, look,
говоришь что надо чтобы сели вот смотри
we came out. Come on, now you and I
мы вышли Давай мы сейчас мы с тобой
can stop this war. Tell us who we
можем остановить эту войну Скажи кого
need, who started it, so that we can
надо кого кто это затеял Чтобы мы
take it. Let us bring them.  let's seat you at
взяли Давай мы их приведём посадим за
the table
стол
Who are we you can't escort yourself to the kitchen
Кто кто мы ты себя не можешь на кухню
Who are you going to Prive revo
проводить кого ты собрался Приве
pri not sha who started the Armed Forces Well look, I
при не ша кто затеял ВС Ну смотри вот я
know what Putin started That is, it turns out that you are
знаю что затеял Путин То есть получается
ready to bring Putin to
ты готов привести Путина на
negotiations I I recently studied
переговоры я я как-то недавно изучал
the theory of three  handshakes, I greeted Putin even
теорию трх рукопожатий я с Путиным даже
after three handshakes with Zelensky, I
через три рукопожатия недоро Зеленским я
greeted Zelensky with one handshake and in
здоровался и
person personally Yes And so what kind of guy is he?
лично лично Да А так он мужик какой
normal Well, I communicated with him in the form of
вообще об нормальны Ну я с ним в образе
politics, but not in the form of Well, something like
политики общался а в не образе Ну типа
that in the form of politics, I did not communicate with him, a
такого что образе политики я с ним не
good guy Well, I don’t know in life,
общался хороший мужик Ну не знаю в жизни
maybe he’s good Maybe he’s bad, I absolutely don’t
может хороший Может плохой абсолютно не
know, so let’s
знаю так вот давай
shake hands with one hand or
получается через одно руко пожать или
directly Yes, so that  uh, bring him to
напрямую Да чтобы э он привести его на
negotiations And on your side, whoever you
переговоры А с вашей стороны кого тогда
need then can bring Putin to
надо сможете привести Путина на
negotiations But we are not listened to, we are the
переговоры А нас не слушают же мы
younger generation And I understand that you, the
молодое поколение А понял то есть вы
younger generation, can only shout
молодое поколение только можете кричать
at the chat roulette as a Ukrainian This is it  all that
в чать рулетке украинцем Вот это всё что
you are allowed is yes I adore you I love you
Вам разрешают да Я обожаю вас у вас лю
No, wait, that is, I correctly understood
Не ну подожди То есть я правильно понял
that you mean nothing in your country, no
что вы в своей стране ничего не значите
one listens to you, all you can do
вас никто не слушает всё что вы можете
is shout to the Ukrainians on chatroulette, but they
это кричать украинцам в чатрулетке тно
don’t listen to me Because I’m not a
меня не слушают Потому что я не
political person  I can’t make
политический человек я не могу принимать
any decisions, invite someone to
какие-то решения звать кого-то на
negotiations, arrange negotiations if I’m
переговоры устраивать переговоры если я
not competent in this, that’s not right. You can,
в этом не компетент не так Ты можешь
for example, take it and look, bros. Let’s
например взять и смотри братва Давайте
leave our club, for example, and tell the
из своего клуба выйдем например и скажем
authorities of Dagestan there. Let’s  Contact
там власти Дагестана Давайте Обратитесь
us, hear us Contact Putin, he
услышьте нас Обратитесь к Путину он вас
will hear you, you can already see it after two
услышит это уже видите через два
handshakes that let’s stop this
рукопожатия что давайте остановим эту
war, we don’t need to kill people in a foreign
войну не нужно нам убивать людей в чужой
country and let our guys from Dagestan
стране и чтобы наши парни из Дагестана
die there, why are
там гибли зачем это вы
you not political, you can’t help but
е ри не политически можеш не
analyze the news Newly watched the
анализировать новость Ново смотрели
news  a bunch You are specifically talking about which ones
новостей куча Ты конкретно про какие
specifically regarding Dagestan and
говоришь именно касательно Дагестана и
mobilization, I know Yes, there were
мобилизации знаю Да были кумыки
handsome Kumyks, so they went out there and broke with the
красавчики так выходили там ломались с
police, they were super
полиции супер
Handsome
Красавцы
wars Yes, no, look, that is, it
во войны Да нене вот смотрите То есть
turns out that you
получается что вы к своему правительству
don’t have any questions for your government Yes, which
никаких вопросов не имеете Да которые
sends your people to war Yes and
отправляет ваших людей на войну Да и
kills people in a foreign country, but go
убивает людей в чужой стране но выходите
to chat roulette and try to
в чат рулетку и что-то пробуете
tell something to the Ukrainians Yes, here you are with such
рассказать украинцам Да вот вы с такой
foam  mouth you prove to me a resident of
пеной у рта доказываете мне жителю
Ukraine who is in Ukraine
Украины который находятся в Украине
who suffers from this aggression of yours
который страдает от этой агрессии вашей
Yes, that everyone knows something is wrong with me.
Да что что-то у меня не так знают все
Maybe you need to tell your guys
Может вам надо вашим ребятам
that something is wrong with them,
рассказывать что что-то у них не так
you, I, here I am  Honestly, I don’t understand, I’ve
вы я вот я честно я не понимаю никогда
never understood people with exactly your
никогда не понимал людей именно вашего
attitude. Look like this. Maybe you
настроя Вот вот так смотри Может тебе
need to talk to people with your attitude.
нужно пообщаться с людьми вашего настроя
Yes, in order to convince them, you don’t have to fight
Да чтобы их переубеждать не надо воевать
in a foreign country, we didn’t come to you,
в чужой стране не мы же к вам пришли не
we’re killing people in Dagestan, it’s true And
мы же убиваем людей в Дагестане правда А
guys  from Dagestan from Buryatia, everyone is
ребята из Дагестана из Бурятии всё
killing people in Ukraine and you looked at
убивают людей в Украине а ты смотрел
the statistics that the largest number of
статистику что наибольшее количество
dead
погибших
Moscow sends Dagestanis to
москви отправляют дагестанцев
die we love heroism, poet That's
погибать любим геройство поэто Вот
right Yes, all national Republics
именно Да все национальные Республики
are sent to  slaughter Yes, but it turns out that
отправляют на убой Да а получается а
Muscovites and St. Petersburg do not die, you
москвичи и Питер не умирают е тему
will raise the topic of Tsarist Russia when Imam
царской России поднимете когда Имам
Shamil will now be imsha you are far away from this
Шамиль сейчас буде имша ты далк от этого
sri Dava is nearby and Dagestan Why
сри Дава воз рядом че и Дагестан Почему
Dastan shi and Chechens No why so No
Дастан ши а чеченцев Нет почему так Нет
three places first place Republic of
три места первое место Республика
Dagestan
Дагестан
second this as  these Buryatia are the third
второе этот как эти Бурятия третья
Chechen Republic like No not not the
Чеченская республика как Нет не не
third mortality statistics no What are you
третья статистика смертности нет Что вы
saying Look and it turns out that you are
говорите Вот смотри и получается что вас
being used simply as an
используют просто как
empire Good you whom you  here in Dagestan,
империи Хорошо Вас кого вас вот дагеста
you live in Dagestan, people who
ты живёшь в Дагестане людей которые
live in Dagestan use a
живут в Дагестане используют
cart of conscription
воза призывного
age oh Okay, well, they haven’t sent you for a whole year Okay, they’ve
возраста ой Окей ну и целый год не
sent them yet Well, look at
отправили Окей ещё отправили Ну смотри а
those guys who were sent Yes,
тех ребят которые которых отправили Да
for some reason, that is, this is your gene pool, yes, that
почему то есть это ваш генофонд да то
is, it
есть
turns out Moscow has been slaughtering you for
получается Москва вас вырезала
centuries And  now she is sending
столетиями А теперь ещё она отправляет
you to a foreign country of young strong men
вас чужую страну молодых сильных мужчин
who could continue the family line.
которые могли бы продолжать род
I’m sitting in the comfort of not in a trench in the
Я вот сижу в комфорте не в окопе в
comfort of a computer, this is a flaw,
комфорте за компьютером это недоработка
yes  flaw guys of age T
да недоработка ребята прино возраста Т
if we have it just like you say,
если у нас тако прям как вы говорите
cutting it out about dressing up the herd they want Yes,
вырезание идт про рядить стадо хотят Да
these
вот эти
words don’t take us away, come
словами нас не забирают вот заходите
here here tse Well, I don’t know what the name of the
сюда тут це Ну я не знаю как называется
computer
компьютерный
club is,
клуб
eh Dado iti I just realized in the game now
э Дадо ити Я просто в игре сейчас понял
yes then  look, maybe we’ll do it so that
да то смотри может сделаем Да чтобы
they come to this club or don’t they
нагрянули в этот клуб или не надо
bend over that the military commissar came to this club and
нагнули что военком пришёл в этот клуб
registered everyone 150 meters from us
переписал всех От нас метров
I understand, yes Yes, it’s really a flaw
150 Поня понял да Да недоработка реально
that there are so many in the club  men are sitting In short,
что столько в клубе мужиков сидит Короче
we have enough people who are playing
играют у нас достаточно людей которые
there Yes, I know, I know Well, no one
туда Да я знаю знаю Ну это ж никто не
argues with you enough Yes,
спорит у вас достаточно Да так вот
look, let us go to the basement Why are you
смотри Давай чтоб мы подвали Почему ты
like that,
так
help me Why do you, understanding that your
ну помоги Почему ты понимая что твоя
country is killing people in a foreign country,
страна убивает людей в чужой стране
go out and say something?  then to prove to the Ukrainians, and
выходишь что-то доказывать украинцам А
not to go out and prove to your
не то чтобы выйти и доказать своим
Russians that there is no need to fight in a foreign
россиянам что не надо воевать в чужой
country, but yes,
стране а а да долетай
fly, fly, I went to the
долетай шёл в
game and again I went to the game I’m back I’m
игру а ещё раз шёл в игру Я вернулся Я
here  Come on, yes, the last question is
здесь Давай да последний вопрос такой
why
вот почему
you why you thank you
ты почему ты спасибо
thank you soar thank you toys look
спасибо реят спасибо игрушки смотри
Why do you understand that your country
Почему ты понимаешь что твоя страна
is killing people in a foreign country Yes, you go out
убивает людей в чужой стране Да выходишь
and try to tell something to the Ukrainians
и что-то пытаешься рассказать украинцам
instead of telling your
вместо того чтобы рассказать своим
Russians that there is no need to fight against a
россиянам что не надо воевать против
Foreign
Чужой
country Why  you don’t want to talk to the Russians,
страны Почему ты с россиянами не хочешь
so I don’t know, I’m here,
поговорить так я не знаю я зал сюда
just talk to the Russians every
просто поговорить с россиянами каждый
day, that’s it, that’s it, talk to the
день гово так вот е надо Говори Смотри с
Russians until the day is over
россиянами доже день пока не закончится
this war until they stop
эта война пока они не перестанут
attacking other
нападать на чужие
countries I just want to talk just
страны Я хочу просто поговорить просто
talk and What do you just want to
поговорить а О чём ты хочешь просто
talk about with the Ukrainians Your country is
поговорить с украинцами Твоя страна их
bombing them And you just want to talk How are you
бомбит А ты хочешь просто поговорить Как
doing I want to know how we are doing like we
ваши дела Хочу узнать как наши дела типа
have to be just let’s say cynical let’s say
надо быть просто скажем циничным скажем
so  go out and ask here the missiles
чтобы выходить и спрашивать тут ракеты
are flying in. How are you doing? No, I
прилетают гово как ваши дела Нет это я
want to ask how you are doing. I’m telling you
хочу спросить как ваши дела Я же говорю
what you value. For
что ты ценишь
example, you go out to people like there in the
ты например выходишь у людей типа там в
city a rocket destroyed a house and you
городе ракета уничтожила дом а ты
go out. Guys, how are you?  you have business And the
выходишь Ребята а как у вас дела А
missile destroyed some civilians Well, who
ракета уничтожила кого мирных Ну да кого
please, open the news, take it to the
ж пожалуйста ну Открой новости возьми в
Dnepropetrovsk house and so on, this is
Днепропетровский дом и так дальше это
hell and that our military can be killed,
раз ад а что военных наших можно убивать
even the military are our people, so
даже военных это наши люди так вот
look when you, here you are, you are absolutely the
смотри когда ты вот вы Вы абсолютно
Lost Youth of the Russian Federation
Потерянная молодёжь Российской Федерации
you grew up all sorts of people there salt wait
вы выросли всяких таких там соля подожди
Listen, I’m already
Послушай я тебе уже
cutting you off on salt yes you are absolutely cynical
подрез на солях да Вы абсолютно циничные
apolitical
аполитичный
who have completely squeezed in the
которые которым зажали полностью в
middle of Russia any opportunity for
середине России любое возможность
self-expression and  all you are allowed to do
самовыражения да и всё что Вам разрешают
is go out to chat roulette and yell
это выходить в чат рулетку и орать
something about Ukrainians, this is the only place
что-то про украинцев это единственное
where you can express your
Где вы можете выплеснуть своё
political position
политическое какую-то позицию так вот
until you stop being slaves in
пока вы не перестанете быть рабами в
your country. So you will be, you
своей стране Так вы будете Вот это
know, who are getting haircuts, Glory to Ukraine,
знаете которых стригут Слава Украине
come on  composition of the
Давай составе
ro like this, all of them come out with
ро вот так вот они выходят все вот эти с
such gentle faces. Yes, but why are
такими нежными лицами Да а что А почему
you Ukrainians so angry with us? I
вы украинцы что-то так на нас злитесь Я
don’t understand everything so well. They
не понимаю так всё Они прекрасно
understand this perfectly well.  the cynical imperial
понимают это и есть циничная имперская
essence of the modern Russian
сущность современной Российской
Federation Yes, these are all federations, they
Федерации Да вот эти все федера они
understand that their country is killing people
понимают что ихняя страна убивает людей
in a foreign country, but
в чужой стране но
they take responsibility for themselves to
они на себя взять ответственность
say Yes, my country is a
сказать Да моя страна
terrorist, they are scared to admit it to themselves,
террорист им страшно Это себе признать
moreover, I will say that
больше того я скажу что
they are completely here, Russia is
они им полностью вот России полностью
completely political  field There you can’t
зачина политическое поле Там нельзя
say anything against Putin, there is no
что-то говорить против Путина там нет
opposition, the only place where a person
оппозиции единственное где человеку
can throw out his emotions is on NATO,
можно выплеснуть свои эмоции Это на НАТО
on Biden, on Zelensky, on the Ukrainians, and
на байдена на Зеленского на украинцев и
they come here and implement this
они сюда выходят и реализуют вот этот
slavish thing of theirs  potential, that is, the
свой такой рабский потенциал то есть
slaves were allowed to shout at the neighboring
рабам разрешили кричать на соседнее
state, but you cannot shout at your
государство но нельзя кричать на своих
slave owners while the Russians are
рабовладельцев пока россияне будут
slaves, that territory will be and life on
рабами та территория будет и жизни на
it will not be normal, our
ней нормальной не будет наша с вами
task is to destroy the Russian Empire, the
задача уничтожить Российскую империю
first stage of the collapse of the Russian Empire
первый этап распада Российской Империи
was in 1917, the second stage of the collapse of the
был в 1917 году второй этап распада
Russian Empire  was in
Российской Империи был в
1991 when the Soviet
1991 году когда развалился Советский
Union collapsed. And now we are on the threshold of the third
Союз И сейчас мы на пороге третьего
final stage of the collapse of the Russian
окончательного этапа распада Российской
Empire, the peoples of the empire must gain
Империи народы империи должны получить
independence, they must get rid of this
независимость должны избавиться от этого
imperial thinking and
имперского мышления и
develop their national states
развивать свои национальные государства
instead of going in and
вместо того чтобы как зомбаки лезть и
conquering foreign countries like zombies Glory to
завоёвывать чужие страны Слава
Ukraine write to my Telegram directly at the same time
Украине пись на мий Telegram прям зараз
VN axis but for now
ось ВН а
it’s even more and more respectful YouTube taking
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through SR Georg to your ban and
нас через СР Георг в твый бан и дуже
not showing too many videos to people  per hour I will not
багато видео не показуе людям в час не
show information about the stream Tom for
показу информация про стрими Тому для
this purpose, Mali is operational  The link
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
will be written directly at once and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video sche tezh Tsikava and Korisna
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry for you
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
trimati postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
pis N
пись N